Dunne, John R.; Papers apap244
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1943-1970; 1; 11.4 cubic ft.
  - Republican County Committee, 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Republican State Committee, 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Request for Voting Records, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Retirement-Pensioners, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Retirement System, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - S, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - S, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Sabbath Laws, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Sales Tax, 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Sales Tax-Exterminators, Undated; 1966 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Sanitarians, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Save Harmless Legislation, 1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Senior Citizen Forms, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Scholar Incentive, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Scholarship Letters, 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Scholarship Letters (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship Letters (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Scholarships, 1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - School Aid Education (1 of 3), 1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - School Aid Education (2 of 3), 1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - School Aid Education (3 of 3), 1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - School Bands, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - School Budgets, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - School Health Service, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - School Lunch Program, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - School Musical Organization-Opposed, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - School Psychologists, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Seat Belts, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Senate, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Senatorial Intern Program, 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Senior Citizens, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Senior Citizens, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Sex Education, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Sex Offenders, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Small Business Development Center, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Social Workers Pay Differential, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Standing Committees of the Senate, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - State Aid, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - State Aid Support, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - State Assembly Districts Map, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - State Committee-Releases, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - State Liquor Authority Report, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - State of New York Annual Budget Message, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - State Police, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Stock Transfer Tax, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Storm King (Power Plant), 1966 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Striped Bass, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Summary of 1966 Legislative Session (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Summary of 1966 Legislative Session (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Surveys, 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - T, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - T, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Tax Increase Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Tax Increase Correspondence, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Tax Increase - Nassau County, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tax Law Deed Stamps, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Tax Relief-Over 65, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Taylor Law-Illegal Strikes, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - TBA-TWA, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Teacher-School Board Relationship, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Teacher, 1966; Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Teachers Retirement Correspondence, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Telephone Company Rate Increase, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Text Books, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Tobacco, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Tours, 1966; Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Transportation, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Transportation, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Transportation (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Transportation (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Transportation, 1967; Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Transit Strike, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Travel Vouchers, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Travel Vouchers, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Truck Inquiries, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Truck Schedule, 1966; Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Unemployment, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Unicameralism, 1961; 1963-1964; 1966 (Flat-file 2)
  - Unicameralism, Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Urban Redevelopment, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Urban Renewal, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Utilities, 1966; Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - V, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - V, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Valley Stream Lake Park, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Vase, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Veterans, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Veterans Bonus Bill, 1966; Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Veteran's Exemption or Real Estate, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Veto Approval Messages (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Veto Approval Messages (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Veto Approval Messages (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Village Clerks, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Village Codes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Village Taxes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Vocational, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Vocational-Access Legis, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Volunteer Fire Department, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Volunteer Fire Depts., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Volunteer Fire Departments State Benefits, Undated; 1966 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - W, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - W, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Wartburg Home, 1966; Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Water Authority, 1968; Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Water Pollution, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Water Pollution, 1967; Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - WCBS-Editorial, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Welfare, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Welfare, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Welfare, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Correspondence, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Whale's Lounge, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Wins, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - WJC to JRD, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - WMCA, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Workmen's Compensation-Self-Insurance, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Work Release Hearings, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Work Release-Nassau County, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Work Release Statements from Hearings (1 of 2), 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Work Release Statements from Hearings (2 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Wydler, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Wydler, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - XYZ, 1967; Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - XYZ, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - XYZ, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Youth, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Youth, 1966 (Flat-file 3)
  - Youth, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Hearing Bill, 1968; Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Legislation, 1960-1970; 2; 4.8 cubic ft.
  Arranged by bill number.
  This series contains bills that John Dunne introduced and voted on in the New York State Senate. Many files also contain supporting materials.
  - A-2, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A-15, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A-25, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A-124, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A-129, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A-145, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - A-154, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A-155, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A-157, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A-158, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A-171, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A-372, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A-375, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A-394, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A-399, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - A-515, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A-529, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - A-559, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - A-615, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A-659, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - A-660, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - A-701, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - A-784, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - A-862, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - A-876, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - A-880, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - A-932-1770, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - A-941, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - A-949, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - A-962, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - A-995, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - A-1037, 1072, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - A-1129, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - A-1181, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - A-1188, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - A-1243, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - A-1320, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - A-1407, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - A-1510, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - A-1521, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - A-1524, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - A-1530, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - A-1563, 1564, 1565, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - A-1600, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - A-1663, 1569, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - A-1724, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - A-1753, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - A-1822, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - A-1909, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - A-2035, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - A-2013, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - A-2351, Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - A-2411, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - A-2562, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - A-2568, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - A-2912, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - A-3734, Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - A-3781, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - A-4195, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - A-4378, Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - A-4661, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - A-4670, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - S.3A, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - S.8, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - S.12, (S.4084, A.6009), (5), 1967-1968; Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - S.16, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - S.19-A, 1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - S.28, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - S.29, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - S.32, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - S.44, Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - S.55, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - S.60, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - S.70, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - S.74, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - S.100, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - S.106, Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - S.108, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - S.131, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - S.136, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - S.137, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - S.138, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - S.139, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - S.140, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - S.141, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - S.143, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - S.161, Undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - S.170, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - S.201, Undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - S.203, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - S-213, Undated; 1967 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - S.218, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - S.219, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - S.220, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - S.226, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - S.227, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - S.228, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - S.229, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - S.230, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - S.238, 240, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - S.239, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - S.241, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - S.246, Undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - S.248, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - S.249, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - S.255, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - S.264, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - S.265, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - S.274, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - S.279, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - S.281, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - S.285, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - S.286, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - S.287, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - S.288, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - S.292, 1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - S.295, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - S.315, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - S.318, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - S.327, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - S.330, 1965-1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - S.336, Undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - S.337, Undated (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - S.346, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - S.347, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - S.348, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - S.437-A, Undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - S.360, Undated (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - S.371, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - S.376, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - S.402, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - S.419, Undated (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - S.425, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - S.437-A, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - S.440, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - S.448, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - S.452, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - S.453-B, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - S.456, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - S-482, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - S.489, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - S.493, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - S-496, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - S.498, Undated (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - S.499-A, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - S-513, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - S-520, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - S.527, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - S-545, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - S-546, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - S-547, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - S-557, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - S-558, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - S-562-A, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - S-569, Undated (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - S-571, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - S-572, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - S-579, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - S-581, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - S-582, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - S-583, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - S-587, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - S-588-A, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - S-590, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - S-592, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - S-614, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - S-616, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - S-618, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - S-619, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - S-625, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - S-626, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - S.633, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - S-635, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - S-642, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - S-643, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - S-646, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - S-647, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - S-652, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - S-655, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - S-659, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - S-661, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - S-662, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - S-663, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - S-664, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - S-665, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - S-666-A, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - S-667, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - S.667, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - S.668, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - S-670, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - S-675, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - S-676, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - S-677, Undated (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - S-680, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - S-691, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - S-702, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - S-706A, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - S-714, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - S-717, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - S-728, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - S-730, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - S-732, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - S-741, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - S-745, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - S-749, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - S-748-A, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - S-750, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - S-756, Undated (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - S-770, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - S-771, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - S-771, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - S-775, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - S-779, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - S-790, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - S-805, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - S-806, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - S-815A, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - S-820, S-1285, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - S.822, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - S-825, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 220)
  - S-828A, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - S-830, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - S-847, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - S.851, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 224)
  - S-854, 1965; 1967 (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - S-856, Undated (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - S-858A, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - S-860, Undated (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - S-871, S-1555, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - S.872/A.1510, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - S-878, Undated (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - S-883-A, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - S-887, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 233)
  - S-894, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 234)
  - S-902, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 235)
  - S.904, [S.4084, A.6009], 1967-1968; Undated (Box 1, Folder 236)
  - S-907, Undated (Box 1, Folder 237)
  - S-913, Undated (Box 1, Folder 238)
  - S-917, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 239)
  - S-924, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 240)
  - S.929/A.1548, 1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 241)
  - S.928/A.1546, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 242)
  - S-929, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 243)
  - S-937, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 244)
  - S-939, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 245)
  - S-950, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 246)
  - S-951, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 247)
  - S-959, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 248)
  - S-960, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 249)
  - SI-1004, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - S.1005-B/A.1585-B, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - S-1019, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - S.1024, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - S-1030, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - S-1042, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - S-1044, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - S-1048, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - S-1050, 1051, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - S-1051, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - S.1059/S.1059-A, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - S-1060, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - S-1061, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - S-1062, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - S-1069, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - S-1076, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - S.1106, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - S-1108, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - S-1116, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - A-1124, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - S-1126, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - S-1144, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - S-1170, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - S.1179, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - S-1191, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - S-1193, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - S.1204, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - S.1205, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - S.1206-A, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - S.1207, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - S.1208, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - S.1213, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - S-1231, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - S-1242, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - S-1243, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - S.1244, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - S-1245, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - S.1245, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - S-1247, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - S-1250, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - S-1254, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - S.1258, (S.4084/A.6009), 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - S-1262, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - S.1265, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - S-1268, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - S-1268, 2366, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - S-1268, 2366, 5201, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - S-1268A, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - S-1272, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - S-1273, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - S-1284, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - S.1287, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - S-1292, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - S-1293, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - S-1313, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - S-1315, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - S-1322A, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - S-1325, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - S.1325, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - S-1329, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - S.1338, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - S-1339, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - S-1340, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - S-1341, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - S-1342, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - S.1343-A, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - S.1344, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - S.1345, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - S-1350-A, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - S-1353, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - S-1355, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - S.1357, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - S.1358, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - S.1359, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - S-1361, Undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - S.1383, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - S.1384-A, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - S-1386, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - S-1397, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - S-1405, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - S.1411, (S.4084, A.6009), 1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - S-1436, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - S-1437, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - S-1453, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - S-1454, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - S-1458, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - S-1470, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - S.1470/A.2243, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - S.1471/A.2239, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - S.1472/A.2242, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - S.1473/A.2241, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - S.1474/A.2240, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - S.1487/A.2238, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - S.1489, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - S-1493, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - S.1498/A.2252, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - S.1499, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - S-1500, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - S.1501-A, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - S-1513, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - S-1523, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - S-1524, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - S-1527, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - S-1533, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - S-1539, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - S-1540, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - S-1541, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - S-1542, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - S-1543, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - S-1544, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - S-1545, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - S-1546, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - S-1546, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - S-1547, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - S.1548/A.2260, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - S-1556, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - S-1562, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - S.1584, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - S.1569, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - S-1572, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - S.1573, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - S.1574, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - S.1575, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - S.1576/S.1576-A, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - S.1577, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - S.1578, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - S-1579, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - S-1581, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - S-1589, Undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - S-1591, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - S-1598, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - S.1602, A.2126, 1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - S-1606, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - S-1614, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - S-1615, Undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - S-1635, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - S-1642, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - S.1642, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - S.1649, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - S.1650, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - S.1651, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - S.1652, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - S.1653, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - S.1659, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - S-1661, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - S-1668, Undated (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - S.1670 (S.4084/A.6009), 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - S.1670, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - S.1671, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - S-1678, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - S.1680, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - S-1684, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - S-1684, 1685, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - S-1692, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - S-1708, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - S-1713, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - S-1721, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - S-1730, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - S.1740, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - S-1759, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - S-1763, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - S.1764, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - S-1767, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - S.1768, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - S-1775, Undated (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - S.1783, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - S.1792, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - S.1793, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - S-1800, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - S.1802, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - S.1803, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - S-1804, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - S-1814, Undated (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - S-1819, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - S.1854/A.2546, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - S-1892, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - S-1899, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - S-1900, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - S.1903, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - S.1904, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - S.1915, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - S-1925, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - S.1930A/A.2868, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - S.1931/A.2845, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - S.1932/A.2849, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - S.1933/A.2846, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - S.1934/A.2851, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - S.1935/A.2852, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)